brilliance.com 2008-06-17

# Privacy Policy - Diamond & Fine Jewelry Experts - Brilliance + Privacy Policy

| 

##   
Your Privacy

| [](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.brilliance.com&sealid=101) |  Brilliance LLC is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.brilliance.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.   
---|---  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Meira Dickman at 866-737-0754. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

What Information Do We Collect?  
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site. 

Personal Information You Choose to Provide  
We may store and receive any information entered on our web site or gathered by our customer service representatives. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.

Information Provided  
You may provide us personally identifiable information when you Create an Account, Manage your Account, use the Personal Shopper, Email a Friend, and Purchase Merchandise on our site. We ask for information such as your name, address, telephone number, credit card information, e-mail addresses, and shipping address when you visit these various areas of our site. 

What are Cookies?  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. To learn more about cookies, click here. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., tracking partners) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.brilliance.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party.   
  
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies and Log Files?   
As you shop on our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web Server Log Files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Our cookies and log files are not tied to personally identifiable information. 

Email A Friend (Send To A Friend)   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a product or feature (such as designing your own ring), we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email (from you to friend) telling them about the product and providing them a link. We do not store this information for any future purpose. 

Communications From the Site   
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. You will receive response from the site to inquiries, Order Confirmation Emails, and critical service updates such as when our site is down. You may not opt-out of receiving these critical service emails. We will send you our Newsletters/product alerts if you have opted-in on our Create Account page to receive these emails. See "Choice/Opt-out" below to unsubscribe to our newsletters and alerts. 

Sharing Information with Third Parties Service Providers  
We use other third parties to provide credit card processing and shipping services on our site. When you purchase a product from us, we will share credit card and shipping information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes. 

Choice/Opt-out   
We provide you the opportunity to make a choice as to how your personally identifiable information is used when we ask for this information. For example, if you create an account and would like to receive our newsletter and alerts, you may "opt-in" to receive these communications. If at any time your preferences change, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions in each email received, go to Manage Your Account on the site, OR email us at [ customerservice@brilliance.com](mailto:customerservice@brilliance.com). 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

Business Transitions  
As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

How Do We Protect Your Information?   
Internet Commerce  
Brilliance is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our website. We offer the industry standard 128-bit Secure Socket Layer encryption (SSL) through your browser when you purchase merchandise on our site. In addition, Brilliance has partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway, to offer safe and secure credit card transactions for our customer. Authorize.Net manages the complex routing of sensitive information through the credit card processing network. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at privacy@brilliance.com . 

The online store at brilliance.com gives you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information provided. 

How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?    
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing [ privacy@brilliance.com](mailto:privacy@brilliance.com). You may also access and correct your information by logging in to your account and making the desired changes via the Manage My Account feature. 

Certain Disclosures  
We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Site, the users of the Site, and/or our Affiliated Parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of the Site, us, or third parties. 

What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy and all other policies contained on our Web site are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

Note that when on the Live Help area of the site that you will be on a third party site during your online conversation and that you will be sharing that information with this third party. 

Contact Brilliance  
Brilliance, LLC is the sole operator of the brilliance.com Web site. If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write us at the following address: 

Brilliance, LLC  
Attention: Privacy  
1665 Palm Beach Lakes Blvd.  
West Palm Beach, Florida 33401  
Or by email at [privacy@brilliance.com](mailto:privacy@brilliance.com)

Your Consent  
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and any amendments thereto. If we amend our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

Changes To our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Last Updated May 16th, 2007 

|  |  | 

##   QUICK LINKS

## PLANT A TREE

Every time you purchase a product from Brilliance, we will plant a tree on your behalf to offset the carbon footprint of an order.

## LIVE HELP

[](https://server.iad.liveperson.net/hc/70156197/?cmd=file&file=visitorWantsToChat&site=70156197&byhref=1&imageUrl=https://server.iad.liveperson.net/hcp/Gallery/ChatButton-Gallery/English/Retail/1a) [Click here](https://server.iad.liveperson.net/hc/70156197/?cmd=file&file=visitorWantsToChat&site=70156197&byhref=1&imageUrl=https://server.iad.liveperson.net/hcp/Gallery/ChatButton-Gallery/English/Retail/1a) or on the Live Help link at the top of your window to chat online with a Brilliance representative.  |
